Mss.B.W564
American Philosophical Society
- VIA. Works by Others, 1924-2007 (Box OS2, Box 192-209)
  - Assorted Works, 1990-1991; Kanter, I., (Ido) (Box 201)
    Includes: Hidden Information in Hamiltonian Systems with Discrete Weights; Information Theory of a Multilayer Neural Network with Discrete Weights; Storage Capacity of a Multilayer Neural Network with Binary Weights (with E. Barkai); Statistical Mechanics of a Multilayered Neural Network (with E. Barkai and D. Hansel); Eigenvalues of Covariance Matrices: Application to Neural-Network Learning (with Yann Le Cun and Sara A. Solla); Neural Networks and the Solution of Nonlinear Equations (with Eli Eisenstein)
  - Biography of John Archibald Wheeler, 1988; Katzen, Brit (Box 201)
  - Fundamental Limits in Digital Information Processing, 1981; Keyes, Robert W., 1921- (Box 201)
  - Quantitative Criterion of the Applicability of the Classical Description Within the Quantum Theory, 1987; Khalfin, L. A.; Tsirelson, Boris (Box 201)
  - Assorted Works, 1988-1990; Kheyfets, Arkady; LaFave, Norman J., (Norman Joseph), 1958-; Miller, Warner Allen (Box 201)
    Includes: Quantum Insights from Null-Strut Geometrodynamics; Pseudo-Riemannian Geometry on a Simplicial Lattice and the Extrinsic Curavture Tensor; Few Insights into the Nature of Classical and Quantum Gravity via Null-Strut Calculus; Null-Strut Calculus. I. Kinematics; Null-Strut Calculus. II. Dynamics
  - Assorted Works, 1996-2001; Kheyfets, Arkady; Miller, Warner Allen (Box 201)
    Includes: Boundary of a Boundary Principle in Field Theories and the Issue of Austerity of the Laws of Physics; E. Cartan Moment of Rotation in Ashtekar's Self-Dual Representation of Gravitation; Time in Quantum Geometrodynamics; Constant Crunch Coordinates for Black Hole Simulations (with Adrian Gentle, Daniel Holz, Pablo Laguna, and Dierdre Shoemaker)
  - P(4) Affine and Superhamiltonian Formulations of Charged Particle Dynamics; Internal Consistency of Kaluza-Klein Theories (with A. Qadir), 1988-1989; Kheyfets, Arkady; Norris, Larry K. (Box 201)
  - Mach's Principle and Rotating Universes; Gravity Wave Insights to Bianchi Type-IX Universes, 1989-1995; King, David Henry (Box 201)
    Includes seminar entitled: There are No Closed Rotating Universes!
  - Experimental Test of the Universal Validity of Conventional Quantum Mechanics, 1988; Klahr, Carl N. (Box 201)
  - Quest for Unity, The Adventures of Physics, 1999; Klein, Etienne, 1958-; Lachieze-Rey, Marc (Box 201)
  - Mechanisms of the Wave-Packet Collapse and Macroscopic Limits in the Quantum Theory of Measurement; Internal Trace for Detector Variables and the Quantum Theory of Measurement (with Kin-ichi Ohmomo), 1990; Kobayashi, Tsunehiro (Box 201)
  - Microwave Ionization of Excited Hydrogen Atoms: What We Do and Do Not Understand, 1990-1991; Koch, Peter M. (Box 201)
  - Dirac's View of the Nature in 1930; Incidental Thougts Concerning Chaos, 1993-2005; Koga, Toyoki, 1912-2010 (Box 201)
  - Assorted Works, 1992-1993; Kosko, Bart (Box 201)
    Includes: Fuzzy Systems as Universal Approximators; Cool Earth; In Defense of God; Addition as Fuzzy Mutual Entropy; Fuzzy Logic (with Satoru Isaka); Fuzzy Function Approximation with Ellipsoidal Rules (with Julie Dickerson)
  - Thermonuclear Paradigm: Remaining Puzzles, 1999; Kramish, Arnold, 1923-2010 (Box 201)
  - Review of Godel's Collected Works, Volume II, 1990; Kreisel, Georg (Box 201)
  - Philsophy, the Physical Model of Universe, 2003; Krian, Aleksander (Box 201)
  - Gravitation Without Curved Space-time, 2000; Krogh, Kris (Box 201)
  - Assorted Works, 1986-1990; Kuchar, Karel Vaclav, 1935- (Box 202)
    Includes: Hamiltonian Dynamics of Gauge Systems; Covariant Factor Ordering of Gauge Systems; Path Integrals in Parametrized Theories: The Free Relativistic Particle (with James Hartle)
  - Einstein Decade (1905-1915), 1974; Lanczos, Cornelius, 1893-1974 (Box 202)
  - Assorted Works, 1961-1987; Landauer, Rolf (Box 202)
    Includes: Irreversibility and Heat Generation in the Computing Process; Fundamental Physical Limitations of the Computational Process; Fundamental Physical Limitations of the Computational Process: An Informal Commentary; Computation: A Fundamental Physical View; Computation, Measurement, Communication and Energy Dissipation
  - Fifth Field: An Introduction to Suq-Quantum Dynamics [excerpt], 1992; Laszlo, Ervin, 1932- (Box 202)
  - Quantum Physics and Philosophy, 1988; Laurikainen, Kalervo Vihtori (Box 202)
  - Singlet Theory -- Why Mass and Gravity are Quantised, 1993; Lawrence, Mike (Box 202)
  - Penrose Photoproduction Processes: A High Efficiency Energy Mechanism for Active Galactic Nuclei and Quasars, 1979; Leiter, Darryl J.; Kafatos, Minas C. (Box 202)
  - Final Laws--The Derivation of the Physical Constants; Nature and Fundamental Representation of Mathematical and Physical Time, 1989-1996; Leng, W. S., (Wilfrid Spencer) (Box 202)
  - Picture of the Quantum World: From Duality to Unity, 1977; Levy-Leblond, Jean Marc (Box 202)
  - Inflation in Kaluza-Klein Theory: Relation Between the Fine-Structure Constant and the Cosmological Constant, 1998; Li, Li-Xin, 1967-; Gott, J. Richard (Box 202)
  - Problems in Complex Systems, 1990; Li, Wentian (Box 202)
  - Uranium People, 1979; Libby, Leona Marshall, 1919- (Box 202)
  - Ubestemthed i Energi og Temperatur, 1982; Lindhard, J. (Jens); Kalckar, Jorgen (Box 202)
  - Assorted Works, 1994-2005; Lo, C. Y., (Chung Y.) (Box 202)
    Includes: Relativistic Causality, Principle of Equivalence and the Question of Gauge in General Relativity; Einstein's Radiation Formula and Modifications to the Einstein Equation; Comments on Riemannian Geometry in Connection with General Relativity; Einstein's Equivalence Principle and Riemannian Geometry; Special Relativity, the Bending of Light, the Photonic Energy-Stress Tensor and Rectification of Einstein's Equation; Einstein's Equivalence Principle and Time-Dependent Light Speeds under Uniform Gravity; Question of Linearized Gravity and Maxwell-Newtonian Approximation; and correspondence.
  - Gamma Ray Laser Based on Induced Annihilation of Electron-Positron Pairs, 1986; Loeb, Abraham; Eliezer, Shalom (Box 202)
  - Forty Years of the First Attempt at the Electroweak Unification and of the Prediction of the Weak Neutral Boson Zo, 1998; Lopes, J. Leite, (Jose Leite), 1918-2006 (Box 202)
  - Pedagogical Remarks on Free Field Relativistic Wave Equations and their Geometrical Nature, 1996-1998; Lopes, J. Leite, (Jose Leite), 1918-2006 (Box 202)
  - La Misura dell'Universo, 1973; Lucentini, Mauro (Box 202)
  - Baryonic Dark Matter, 1990; Lynden-Bell, D.; Gilmore, Gerry, 1951- (Box 202)
  - Character of Mathematical Research, 1992; Mac Lane, Saunders, 1909-2005 (Box 202)
  - Escape From a Fluctuating Double Well, 1995; Madureira, Antonio J. R., et al (Box 202)
  - Zur Theorie der Schroedingerschen Gleichung, 1927; Mandelstam, Leonid Isaakovich, 1879-1944; Leontowitsch, M. (Box 202)
  - Assorted Works, 1989-1990; Manko, V. S., (Vladimir S.) (Box 202)
    New Stationary Electrovacuum Generalizations of the Schwarzschild Solution (with Ts. Gutsunaev); New Exact Solution for the Exterior Gravitational Field of a Spinning Mass; On the Description of the External Field of a Static Deformed Mass; On a New Static Solution of the Einstein-Maxwell Equations for a Massive Magnetic Dipole; Superposition of the Kerr Metric with the Generalized Erez-Rosen Solution (with Jose Castejon-Amenedo); On Event Horizons in Static Vacuum Spacetimes (with Jose Castejon-Amenedo and Malcolm MacCallum); General Static Axisymmetric Solution of the Vacuum Einstein Equations Possessing a Regular Event Horizon (with Sh. Khakimov; New Axially Symmetric Solutions of the Einstein-Maxwell Equations
  - Maximal Hypersurfaces and Foliations of Constant Mean Curvature in General Relativity, Marsden, Jerrold E.; Tipler, Frank J. (Box 202)
  - On the Origin of Inertial Accelerations, 1991; Mashhoon, Bahram (Box 202)
  - Imaginary-Frequency Interior Modes of Black Holes, 1979; Matzner, Richard A., (Richard Alfred), 1942-; Zamorano, Nelson Arturo (Box 202)
  - Is GX1+4 the Compact 511 keV Galactic-Center Source?, 1989; McClintock, Jeffrey E.; Leventhal, Marvin (Box 202)
  - Paradoxical Nature of Reality, 1973-1976; Melhuish, George (Box 202)
  - La Fission Nucleaire, 1982; Michaudon, Andre (Box 202)
  - Assorted Abstracts, 1988-1990; Mielke, Eckehard W. (Box 202)
  - Contents of Source Book on Quantum Electrodynamics in the 1930s, n.d.; Miller, Arthur I. (Box 202)
  - Airy Integral, 1946; Miller, J. C. P., (Jeffery Charles Percy) (Box 202)
  - Relativistic Fluids in Cosmology, 1967; Misner, Charles W. (Box 202)
  - Collaboration in Creativity [includes interview with Wheeler]; Social Context of Extraordinary Individuals, 1996; Mockros, Carol A. (Box 202)
  - Relativity [Ed. by John A. Wheeler], 1976; Møller, C., (Christian), 1904-1981 (Box 202)
  - Nogle Erindringer fra Liver pa Bohrs Institut i sidste Halvdel af Tyverne (by Moller). Nogle minder on Niels Bohr (by Rosenfeld), 1962; Møller, C., (Christian), 1904-1981; Rosenfeld, L., (Leon), 1904-1974 (Box 202)
  - Riemann Integral Approach to Feynman's Path Integral, 1995; Monaco, R. L.; Lagos, R. E.; Rodrigues, W. A. (Waldyr Alves) (Box 203)
  - Neutrino Propulsion for Interstellar Spacecraft, 1998; Morgan, J. A. (Box 203)
  - Dissonance in the Heavens, n.d.; Morrison, Philip (Box 203)
  - Princeton and the Bomb: Five Professors Recall Their Days at Alamo, 1995; Moseley, Caroline, 1935- (Box 203)
  - Large Scale Structure of the Universe, Its Initial Singularity, and Its Dark Matter; Simple Short Proof of Fermat's Last Theorem, 1989; Motz, Lloyd, 1910-2004 (Box 203)
  - Many-Hilbert-Spaces Theory of Quantum Measurements, 1988; Namiki, Mikio (Box 203)
  - Bending a Lightbeam: A Look at the Gravitational Lens A2390; Quantum Computation upon a Single Electron, 1997; Newbower, David S. (Box 203)
  - Spacetime Foam, 2003-2004; Ng, Yee Jack (Box 203)
  - Limit to Spacetime Measurement, 1993; Ng, Yee Jack; Van Dam, Hendrik, 1934- (Box 203)
  - Non-Uniform Chaotic Dynamics with Implications to Information Processing, 1983; Nicolis,, J., (John), 1934-; Meyer-Kress, G., (Gottfried); Haubs, G. (Box 203)
  - Wheeler Shoots Monkey, Teaches Poets Physics, 1973; Nold, Chip (Box 203)
  - Assorted Works, 1990-1993; Novikov, I. D., (Igor Dmitrievich) (Box 203)
    Includes: Cauchy Problem in Spacetimes with Closed Timelike Curves (with John Friedman, Michael Morris, Fernando Echeverria, Gunnar Klinkhammer, Kip Thorne, and Ulvi Yurtsever); On the Gravitational Field of an Arbitrary Axisymmetric Mass Endowed with Magnetic Dipole Moment (with Vladimir Manko); Jinn of the Time Machine: Nontrivial Self-Consistent Solutions (with A. Lossev); Time Machine and Self-Consistent Evolution in Problems with Self-Interaction; Jinnee of the Time Machine; Inelastic Billiard Ball in a Spacetime with a Time Machine (with E. V. Mikheeva); Encounter of a Star with a Massive Black Hole (with A. Khoklov and C. J. Pethick).
  - Reconstruction of Scientific Theory Change, 1989-1996; Nugayev, Rinat M. (Box 203)
  - Eulerian and Langrangian Gauge Invariance, Nutku, Yavuz (Box 203)
  - R. A. Fisher, Probability Amplitudes, and the Quantum Mechanical Mixed State, 1994-1996; Oaxaca, Candace (Box 203)
  - Possible Isomers in Nuclei Beyond the Drip Lane, 1986; Ogawa, K., (Kengo) (Box 203)
  - Finite Quantum Electrodynamics with a Gravitationally Smeared Propagator, n.d.; Ohanian, Hans C. (Box 203)
  - Big-Bang Nucleosynthesis Revisited, 1989; Olive, Keith A., 1956-; Schramm, David N.; Steigman, Gary, 1941-; Walker, Terrence P., 1958- (Box 203)
  - Bohm Case, n.d; Olwell, Russell B., 1969- (Box 203)
  - Interdependence of the Speed of Light, Inertia, and the Strength of Gravity, 1995; O’Riordan, Christopher B. (Box 203)
  - When and How Physics Contributes to Understanding the Periodic Law?, 2001; Ostrovsky, V. N., (Valentin N.) (Box 203)
  - Did God Have a Choice?, 1999; Overbye, Dennis, 1944- (Box 203)
  - Assorted Works, 1986-1996; Paczynski, Bohdan (Box 203)
    Includes: Gravitational Microlensing by the Galactic Halo; Gravitational Microlensing and the Search for Dark Matter; Gravitational Microlensing in the Local Group
  - Assorted Works, 1982-1988; Padmanabhan, T. (Box 203)
    Includes: General Covariance, Accelerated Frames, and the Particle Concept; Why Does an Accelerated Detector Click?; Response of an Accelerated Detector Coupled to the Stress-Energy Tensor (with T. P. Singh); Principle of General Covariance and Quantum Theory; Semi-Classical Approximations for Gravity and the Issue of Backreaction
  - Observational Consequences of Many-Worlds Quantum Theory, 1999; Page, Don N., (Don Nelson) (Box 203)
  - Question of Origin, End and Existence, 1993; Paily, John (Box 203)
  - Collapse as Spontaneous Unitary Symmetry (Superposition) Breaking in Quantum Mechanics as Unitary Symmetric Quantum Field Theory, n.d.; Pankovic, Vladan, 1961- (Box 203)
  - Quantum Thermodynamics, 1989; Partovi, M. Hossein (Box 203)
  - Primeval Mass Fluctuation Sprectrum and the Distribution of the Nearby Galaxies, 1996; Peebles, P. J. E. (Phillip James Edwin); Wilkinson, David T. (Box 203)
  - Discovery of the 3 oK Radiation, 1990; Peebles, P. J. E. (Phillip James Edwin); Wilkinson, David T. (Box 203)
  - Heritage of Heraclitus: John Archibald Wheeler and the Itch to Speculate, 2002; Pelikan, Jaroslav, 1923-2006 (Box 203)
  - Analysis of the Structure of Space-Time; Emperor's New Mind [excerpts], [1970]-1989; Penrose, Roger (Box 204)
  - Critique of the Wheeler-DeWitt Equation, 1997; Peres, Asher, 1934- (Box 204)
  - Is Quantum Theory Universally Valid?, 1982; Peres, Asher, 1934-; Zurek, Wojciech Hubert, 1951- (Box 204)
  - Assorted Works, 1985-1991; Perlis, Donald, 1944- (Box 204)
    Includes: Autocircumscription; Commensense Set Theory; Languages with Self-Reference I: Foundations; Languages with Self-Reference II: Knowledge, Belief, and Modality; Completeness Results for Circumscription (with Jack Minker); On the Consistency of Commonsense Reasoning; How Can a Program Mean?; Reasoning Situated in Time I: Basic Concepts (with Jennifer Elgot-Drapkin)
  - Principle of Identicality and the Foundations of Quantum Theory, 1989; Pesic, Peter D. (Box 204)
  - Demons, Engines and Information: Can a Clever Demon Outsmart the Second Law of Thermodynamics?, 1990; Peterson, Ivars (Box 204)
  - Signaling by Photon Counting: The Capacity of a Photon Channel with Noise, 1977; Pierce, John R. (Box 204)
  - Conjectures and Refutations [excerpt], 1976; Popper, Karl R., (Karl Raimund), 1902-1994 (Box 204)
  - Assorted Works, 1959-2005; Pugh, George Edgin, 1926- (Box 204)
    Includes: Proposal For a Satellite Test of the Coriolis Prediction of General Relativity; Roots of Gravity Probe-B; Recollections of Hugh Everett III; correspondence.
  - Photon Scattering by the Statistical Atom, 1959; Putnam, Peter (Box 204)
  - To Preserve the Scientific Spirit, 1956; Rabi, I. I., (Isidor Isaac), 1898-1988 (Box OS2)
    Oversized. Article in February 12, 1956 issue of New York Times Magazine
  - Is There a Viable Hidden Variable Approach to Quantum Theory?, 1993-1994; Raezer, S. D., (Spencer D.) (Box 204)
  - Relativity Revisited, 1994; Raiford, Maurice T. (Box 204)
  - Empirical Approach of the Theory of Particle and Nuclear Phenomena, 1999; Ramanna, Raja, 1925-2004 (Box 204)
  - It From Bit and Perception, 2000; Rao, Gopala U. V. (Box 204)
  - Interdependent Trilogy on the Ordinal Nature of Quantum Sets; Does Wheeler's Self-Observing Universe have Astigmatism?, 1993; Raptis, Ioannis (Box 204)
  - Assorted Works, 1968-1993, n.d.; Reynolds, George T. (Box 204)
    Includes: Interference Effects Produced by Single Photons (with K. Spartalian and D. B. Scarl); Image Intensification Applied to Observations of Crystalloluminescence; Sources of Low Level Light Emission in Laboratory and Sea Water; War Experience: Los Alamos
  - Universe, 2000; Roseborough, Trevor (Box 204)
  - Assorted Works, 1950-1963; Rosenfeld, L., (Leon), 1904-1974 (Box 205)
    Includes: Professor Einstein's Dilemma; Niels Bohr. An Essay Dedicated to him on the Occasion of his Sixtieth Birthday; Le Conflit Epistemologique entre Einstein (in French); Niels Bohr, 7 October 1885 - 18 November 1962 (also includes "Niels Bohr at Work" by Stefan Rozental).
  - Boscovich Covariance, 1989; Rossler, Otto, 1907-1991 (Box 205)
  - Syntax, Semantics and the Problem of the Identity of Mathematical Objects, 1985-1986; Rota, Gian-Carlo, 1932-1999; Sharp, D. H., (David Howland), 1938-; Sokolowski, Robert (Box 205)
  - Assorted Works, 1991-1993; Rovelli, Carlo, 1956- (Box 205)
    Includes: On Quantum Mechanics; Ashtekar Formulation of General Relativity and Loop-Space Non-Perturbative Quantum Gravity: A Report; Basis of the Ponzano-Regge-Turaev-Viro-Ooguri Quantum-Gravity Model is the Loop Representation Basis
  - Assorted Works, 1998-2000; Ruffini, Remo (Box 205)
    Includes: Memorandum of Uunderstanding between ICRA and UNESCO on the Development of the ICRA Network of International Centres of Relativistic Astrophysics; Dyadosphere of Black Holes and Gamma-Ray Bursts; On Evolution of the Pair-Electromagnetic Pulse of a Charged Black Hole (with Jay Salmonson, James Wilson, and She-Sheng Xue; Black Hole Formulation and Gamma Ray Bursts
  - Early Magnetic Field and Primeval Satellite System of the Moon, 1994; Runcorn, S. K. (Box 205)
  - Nuclear Collective Motion: Markovian or Not?; Self-Consistent Transport Tensors for Collective Motion in Several Dimensions, 1989; Samhammer, Raimund; Hofmann, Helmut, 1941-; Yamaji, S., (Shuhei) (Box 205)
  - Natural Mathematics, God and World, 1994; Savchenko, Yevgeny V., (Yevgeny Vladimirovich) (Box 205)
  - Note: John Mitchell and Black Holes, 1979; Schaffer, Simon, 1955- (Box 205)
  - Energy Flow and Frequency Spectrum About Electric and Magnetic Dipoles, 1995; Schantz, Hans (Box 205)
  - Boundary Value Problem for the Stationary and Axisymmetric Einstein Equations is Generically Solvable, Schaudt, Urs M.; Pfister, Herbert, 1936- (Box 205)
  - Does Thermodynamics Rule Out the Existence of Cosmological Singularities?, 1989; Schiffer, Marcelo (Box 205)
  - Assorted Works, 1987-1997; 2.0 folders; Schleich, Wolfgang (Box 205)
    Includes: Delayed-Choice Experiments in Quantum Interference (with T. Hellmuth, H. Walther, and A. Zajonc); Interference in Phase Space; Phase Space, Correspondence Principle and Dynamical Phases: Photon Count Probabilities of Coherent and Squeezed States via Interfering Areas in Phase Space; Das Teilchen im Kasten: Strukturen in der Wahrscheinlichkeitsdichte (in German); correspondence.
  - Quantum Numbers of Orientation -- the Geometric Meaning of the Quarks -- Representations of O in C13,1 and SU(3), 1993; Schmeikal, Bernd, 1946- (Box 205)
  - Quasars, 1967; Schmidt, Maarten, 1929- (Box 205)
  - Explosive Nucleosynthesis, 1973; Schramm, David N.; Arnett, W. David (William David), 1940- (Box 205)
  - Definite Quantum Measurements, 1990; Schulman, L. S., (Lawrence S.), 1941- (Box 205)
  - Gravity From the Ground Up, 1991; Schutz, Bernard F. (Box 205)
  - Cosmology [Ed. by John A. Wheeler], 1975; Sciama, D. W. (Dennis William), 1926- (Box 205)
  - Science and Ultimate Reality: Celebrating the Vision of John Archibald Wheeler and Taking It Forward into a New Century of Discovery, 2002; Science & Ultimate Reality Symposium. (2002: Princeton, N.J.) (Box 205)
  - Mathematical Implications of Fundamental Physical Principles, 1989; Segal, Irving Ezra (Box 205)
  - James Clerk Maxwell (1831-1879); Member APS 1875. Builder of Bridges Between Isaac Newton and Albert Einstein, 2001; Seitz, Frederick, 1911-2008 (Box 206)
  - Computational Neuroscience, 1988-1990; Sejnowski, Terrence J., (Terrence Joseph); Koch, Christof, 1956-; Churchland, Patricia Smith (Box 206)
  - Before and During the Big Bang, 1998; Shearer, Jack Nevin, 1927- (Box 206)
  - Assorted Works, 1988-1998; Shih, Yanhua (Box 206)
    Includes: New Type of Einstein-Podolsky-Rosen-Bohm Experiment Using Pairs of Light Quanta Produced by Optical Parametric Down Conversion (with C. O. Alley); Einstein-Podolsky-Rosen-Bohm Experiment Using Pairs of Light Quanta Produced by Type-II Parametric Down Conversion (with T. E. Kiess, A. V. Sergienko, and C. O. Alley); Experiemental Evaluation of a Two-Photon Wave Packet in Type-II Parametric Downconversion; Two-Photon Geometric Optics (with T. B. Pittman, D. V. Strekalov, D. N. Klyshko, M. H. Rubin, and A. V. Sergienko); Popper's Experiment: Uncertainty, Entanglement, and Action-at-a-Distance; Two-Photon Entanglement and Quantum Reality
  - Wigner's Contributions to the Quantum Theory of Measurement; Can the Fundamental Laws of Nature be the Results of Evolution?, 1998; Shimony, Abner (Box 206)
  - Secondary Infall Model of Galactic Halo Formation and the Spectrum of Cold Dark Matter Particles on Earth, 1996; Sikivie, P.; Tkachev, I. I.; Wang, Y., (Yun) (Box 206)
  - Gravitational Waves from Outer Space, 1973; Simen, Rolf H. (Box 206)
  - Neutron Oscillation as a Source of Excess Sub-GeV Antiprotons in Galactic Cosmic Rays, 1982; Sivaram, C.; Krishan, V. (Vinod) (Box 206)
  - Books for Developing Countries: The Franklin Book Programs, 1983; Smith, Datus Clifford, b. 1907 (Box 206)
  - Assorted Works, 1980-1981; Sobczyk, Garret, 1943- (Box 206)
    Includes: Complex Gibbs-Heaviside Vector Algebra for Spacetime; Conjugations and Hermitian Operators in Spacetime; Spacetime Vector Analysis; Algebraic Classification of Important Tensors in Physics
  - Topological Approach to Quantum Theory, 1992; Sokolov, Igor Yu (Box 206)
  - Measurement; Los Alamos as a Project in Philosophy, 1987-1996; Sokolowski, Robert (Box 206)
  - Podkletnov Dynamics: Three Hypotheses [excerpts], 2000; Solov, G. (Box 206)
  - Selected Papers of Lyman Spitzer, Jr.: Commentary, Paper #18, 1971; Spitzer, Lyman, 1914-1997 (Box 206)
  - Pioneer of Thought, 1987; Stanley, Dick (Box 206)
  - Assorted Works, 1990-1998; Stapp, Henry P. (Box 206)
    Includes: EPR and Bell's Theorem: A Critical Review; Quantum Measurement and the Mind-Brain Connection; Quantum Theory of the Mind-Brain Interface; Quantum Conception of Man
  - Big Bang Nucleosynthesis: The Standard Model, 1988; Steigman, Gary, 1941- (Box 206)
  - One-dimensional Motion for Classical Relativistic Two-body Systems in Time-asymmetric Lorentz Scalar Potentials, 1985-1989; Stephas, Paul (Box 206)
  - Origin of Life, 1998; Strimling, Gene (Box 206)
  - Ground States of a Few Gravitating Neutrons, 1978-1981; Strobel, George L. (Box 206)
  - Black Hole Statistics, n.d.; Strominger, Andrew (Box 206)
  - Chaos, Stability and Predictability in Newtonian Dynamics, 1990; Szebehely, Victor G., 1921- (Box 206)
  - Enhanced Radiation Driven by a dc Electric Field, 1989; Tajima, Toshiki; Benz, A. O. (Arnold O.); Thaker, M.; Lebouef, J. N. (Box 206)
  - Distance of the Virgo Cluster -- A Review, 1987; Tammann, G. A. (Box 206)
  - Pulsating Universe: Review and Latest Development, 2000; Tangherlini, Frank (Box 206)
  - Assorted Works, 1995-2000; 2.0 folders; Tavani, M., (Marco) (Box 206)
    Includes: Science with AGILE; Euclidean versus Non-Euclidean Gamma-Ray Bursts; Shock Emission Model for Gamma-Ray Bursts; Pions, Supernovae, and the Supra-Nuclear Matter Density Equation of State (with Ronald Mayle and James Wilson); Theory of High-Energy Emission from the Pulsar/Be-star System PSR 1259-63 I: Radiation and Interaction Geometry (with Jonathan Arons); Dual Nature of Hard X-Ray Outbursts from the Superluminal X-Ray Transient Source GRO J1655-40 (Tavani et al)
  - Boundaries of Nature: Special and General Relativity and Quantum Mechanics, a Second Course in Physics, 1998; Taylor, Edwin F. (Box 206)